<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John&#39;s Two Cents</title>
    <link>http://johnski001.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on John&#39;s Two Cents</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-BE</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 07:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://johnski001.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Subatomic a game about cool physics and chemistry!</title>
      <link>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/subatomic-a-game-about-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/subatomic-a-game-about-physics/</guid>
      <description>A cool thing about playing boardgames is that from time to time you can really learn something. In Subatomic you can learn a lot about cool physics and chemistry!
This game is a game that I backed on Kickstarter a couple of years ago and has been played a couple of times with my kids back in the day. The coolest thing about this is that I have a numbered edition, I have 224 out of 3400!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonos on a different vlan using the Unifi USG</title>
      <link>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/sonos-on-different-vlan-using-usg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 07:00:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/sonos-on-different-vlan-using-usg/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I have been doing some changes on my home network that involved vlanning. Of course, when you say vlan &amp;amp; Sonos in one sentence you&amp;rsquo;ve got to make ready for some issues. You can find my lessons learned in this blog. I can tell you that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy to overcome this.
Situation My network looks a little bit like this:
 Vlan: Internet of things Vlan: End user devices Lan with all the Unifi devices  I&amp;rsquo;m using a Unifi Cloudkey Gen2 plus as my Unifi controller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamdeck Installation on Linux</title>
      <link>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/streamdeck-installation-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/streamdeck-installation-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays streaming is a widely practiced hobby. Gaming, e-sports, etc&amp;hellip; are all things that aid to the popularity of streaming as a whole. A lot of people dream about streaming content for a living and for that you need to have a setup that enables you to do a lot of different stuff on stream, there comes the Streamdeck into play. The Streamdeck is actually a buttonbox that you can program with all kinds of functionality to enhance your streams or even you worklife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This blog costs less then 10$ per year</title>
      <link>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/this-blog-costs-less-then-ten-dollars-per-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/this-blog-costs-less-then-ten-dollars-per-year/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it is possible. You can run a website for virtually no money thanks to a couple of software and services. Actually, you don&amp;rsquo;t need a full fledged CMS for a personal website.
 A CMS is the abbreviation of a content management system and is a website that&amp;rsquo;s built around a database and forms to add content to the website. This means a lot of code that can be abused by not so friendly visitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to John&#39;s two cents</title>
      <link>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 17:11:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnski001.com/post/2022/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
After some years of absence in the blog-o-sphere, I decided to start writing again. After running a successfull blog for quite some time I was ready to take some time off as running the blog was too time-consuming.
I had the joy back then to organize Blogosphere, a meetup for Belgian bloggers, work with PR agencies and attend different press events. I guess I did all what I wanted to achieve back in the day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
